PURNA CHANDRA SAHU

Assistant Manager-Risk Advisory SAP Security & GRC

ightharpoonup purna.chandra.1618@gmail.com ightharpoonup +91-9556572845 ightharpoonup purna-chandra-sahu ightharpoonup pc-purna ightharpoonup Passport: Z3466886

PROFILE SUMMARY

Purna Chandra brings in over 5.8 years of IT experience and is currently Assistant Manager in Risk Advisory practice of Deloitte India. His experience spans across SAP Security & GRC. Specialized in SAP GRC Access controls, SAP ECC, S4HANA, Fiori & BI Security concepts and worked on Implementation projects and Managed Services.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Deloitte Touché Tohmastu India LLP

Bengaluru, Karnataka

Oct 2022 - Present

Assistant Manager-Risk Advisory

SAP GRC:

- Experience in E2E Access Control implementation [ARA, EAM, ARM, BRM, UAR and SOD risk review modules].
- Experience in creating test scripts for the above-mentioned GRC AC modules.
- Experience in design, analysis and build of SAP GRC SoD ruleset worked on Mitigation controls, Risks and Functions.
- SAP SuccessFactors and SAP ECP integration with SAP GRC for Cross-system risk analysis and access provisioning.
- Experience in configuring and enhancing FF Log review workflow involving analysis of SOD and Critical actions.
- Experience in SAP GRC RM configuration and master data creation.

SAP S4HANA/Fiori:

- Fiori Catalog and Group creation for S4HANA; Fiori Spaces and Pages creation for S4HANA
- Activation of OData services SICF nodes.
- Fiori role building and SU24 authorisation maintenance.
- Fiori Application issue troubleshooting using IWFND/ IWBEP Error logs, Brower console and application logs.

SAP ECC:

- GRC access control EAM relevant SPRO configuration.
- Master data/testing scenario creation for FF Log Review workflow.

➤ Client: Unilever, India

Environment: SAP GRC AC 12.0, SAP ECC

Key Responsibility:

- GRC EAM configuration and master data preparation.
- FF Log review workflow enhancement Made relevant MSMF workflow changes.
- Test script creation and E2E testing on FF Log review workflow.
- > Client: Cameco, Canada

Environment: SAP GRC AC 12.0, SAP S4HANA, SAP ECP, SAP SuccessFactors

Key Responsibility:

- SAP GRC Access Control E2E Implementation.
- Cross system risk analysis for SAP SFEC, S4 and ECP Configuration and SoD Ruleset built.
- SAP SFEC and SAP ECP integration with SAP GRC 12 embedded in SAP S4HANA.
- S4HANA Role building, Fiori App customisation Fiori Catalogs & Group.
- Fiori App Authorisation issue troubleshooting.

➤ Client: Ashok Leyland, India

Environment: SAP GRC AC 12.0, SAP ECC

Key Responsibility:

- SAP GRC AC Implementation.
- SAP GRC RM Implementation SPRO configuration and Master Data preparation.

IBM India Pvt. Ltd

Kolkata, West Bengal

July 2018 - October 2022

 $Package\ Specialist\ -\ SAP\ Security\ \ \ GRC$

SAP ECC, ISU, C4C, Fiori:

- Experience in design and building of SAP PFCG roles as per business requirement.
- Experience in maintenance of User Master Records, Authorization Groups/Profiles/Roles to R/3 users.
- Authorisation Object Maintenance using SU24.
- Analyse and troubleshoot security issues using SU53, ST01, STAUTHTRACE, SLG1 and SUIM.
- Experience with SECATT scripts for mass password creation in ECC, role assignment and SODA limit assignment.
- Worked with CUA and Non-CUA Environments. Knowledge about CUA configuration over the SAP landscape.
- Worked in SAP Support portal for managing OSS, Developer Access key & Object access key creation.
- Performed Monthly House-keeping clean-up activities.

SAP GRC:

- Worked on GRC ARA, EAM, ARM modules.
- Risk Analysis during Role build and User access assignment.
- Report extraction for audit and re-certification activities.

SAP BI /BW:

- Build Analysis Authorizations using the transaction RSECADMIN and Role maintenance.
- Troubleshoot analysis authorizations related problems using RSECADMIN.

SAP BOBJ:

- User administration and access assignment to end users as per requirement.
- Performed Monthly House-keeping clean-up activities.
 - > Client: Thames Water Utilities Ltd, UK

Environment: SAP ECC 6, ISU, C4C, GRC AC (10.1,12), Fiori, BI 7, CRM

Key Responsibility:

- Provided production and non-production support for various SAP systems such as SAP ECC, ISU, BI/BW, C4C, GRC, Fiori, and CRM.
- Supported for SAP Security controls and User Access Reviews process, conducted SOD and user access analysis under Risk Analysis and Remediation.
- Authorization object maintenance in SU24.
- Supported in audits performed by client and external vendors.
- Performed critical analysis on EWA reports from SAP Security perspective produced monthly or quarterly.
- Worked in Migration Activities from SAP Security perspective and managed Team Members for the same for Project deliveries.
- SAP License Audit: Usage of SLAW2 and USMM to extracting SAP Licence usage in the systems and provide the consolidated report to external and SAP auditors.
- Perform KT sessions for the new Joiners in the Team and guide them about Project activities from SAP Security perspective.

EDUCATION

International Institute of Information Technology

Bhubaneswar

Course: Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science and Engineering

August 2014-June 2018

• Cumulative GPA: 8.02

Vyomayana Samstha Vidyalaya

Sunabeda

Course: Senior Secondary School | 12th Grade(CBSE)

April 2013–June 2014

• Percentage: 91.2 %

Course: Secondary School | 10th Grade(CBSE)

April 2011-June 2012

• Cumulative GPA: 10.0

SKILLS & INTERESTS

Industry Served: Energy & Utilities; Consumer Products

SAP Applications: GRC 10.1 & 12.0, S4HANA, ECC, Fiori, ISU, C4C, HANA, BW, BOBJ **Trainings:** SAP Security; SAP GRC(AC, PC, RM); SAP HANA Security; SAP BTP(Basic) **Tools used:** Transport Expresso; Azure DevOps; HP ALM; Service Now; Octane ALM

Language: C, C++, Java, Python, SQL

Interests: Problem-solving, Analytics, Cybersecurity, Data Science, Cyptography

SPECIALIZATION

- SAP GRC Access Control (10.1, 12.0)
- SAP Security User & Role Administration
- SAP Implementation and Managed services

CERTIFICATIONS

SAP Certified Application Associate SAP Access Control 12

 $\mathrm{July}\ 2022$

AWS Cloud Practitioner Certification

August 2021-August 2024

Energy & Utilities Industry Foundations

March 2019

ACHIEVEMENTS

Got multiple Recognition Awards at Deloitte.

Got multiple Manager's Choice Awards at IBM.

Got Spark Award - Cash Reward for being the Top performer in project at IBM.